Guide to the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 77 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- MEETING MINUTES, 1897-1988; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-4/19, 6/1-9/33, 11/1-14/18)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 147, Halls Lake, 1956-1963; Subseries VV (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Minutes: Unit 147 A and BA Halls Lake, WA, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 148, Newport-Locke, 1958-1977; Subseries WW (Box-folder 6/12-6/14)
    - Minutes: Unit 148 A Newport-Locke, WA Part I, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Minutes: Unit 148 A Newport-Locke, WA Part II, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Minutes: Unit 148 A Newport- Locke, WA, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 149, Beaverton, Oregon, 1961-1963; Subseries XX (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Minutes: Unit 149 Beaverton, OR, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - IBEW 77, Unit 150, Coos Bay, Oregon, 1961-1963; Subseries YY (Box-folder 6/16)
    - Minutes: Unit 150 Coos Bay, OR, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - IBEW 77, Local 944 and 952, 1919-1927; Subseries ZZ (Box-folder 11/1-11/2, 11/5, 11/7)
    - Minutes International Brotherhoood of Electrical Workers Local 952, 1919-1923 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Minutes International Brotherhoood of Electrical Workers Local 944, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Minutes International Brotherhoood of Electrical Workers Local 944, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Minutes International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 944, 1919 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - IBEW 77, Safety Committee, 1947-1949; Subseries AAA (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Minutes: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers B77 Safety Committee, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 12/13)
- CONTRACTS, 1936-2003; SERIES II (Box-folder 5/1-5/11, 10/1-10/24)
  - Contracts: Seattle Hotel Association, 1951-1980 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Contracts: Seattle Steam Corporation, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Contracts: Seattle Transit System, 1944-1956 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Contracts: Shelton Joint Power Operation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Contracts: Simpson Power Plant, Shelton, WA, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Contracts: Snohomish County Public Utility District No. 1, 1951-1967 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Contracts: Snohomish County Public Utility District No. 1, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Contracts: Snohomish County Public Utility District No. 1, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Contracts: Washington Water and Power Company, 1940-1958 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Contracts: Washington Water and Power Company, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Contracts: West Coast Telephone Company and the Northwest Communications Council, 1952-1964 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Contracts: Bellingham Gas, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Contracts: Benton County Public Utility District No. 1, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Contracts: Chelan County Public Utility District No. 1, 1954-1967 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Contracts: Centralia Department of Lighting, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Contracts: Cowlitz County Public Utility District No. 1, 1953-1981 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Contracts: City of Ellensburg, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Contracts: General Telephone Company of the Northwest, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Contracts: Grant County Public Utility District No. 2, 1955-1978 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Contracts: Grays Harbor County Public Utility District No. 1, 1958-1981 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Contracts: Interstate Telephone Company, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Contracts: Lewis County Public Utility District No. 1, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Contracts: Mason County Public Utility District No. 3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Contracts: Northwest Line Constructors Chapter, National Electrical Contractor's Association, 1955-1975 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Contracts: Northwest Line Constructors Chapter, National Electrical Contractor's Association, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Contracts: Pacific County Public Utility District No. 2, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Contracts: Pend Oreille County Public Utility District No. 1, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Contracts: Puget Sound Power and Light Company, 1936-1952 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Contracts: Puget Sound Power and Light Company, 1953-1968 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Contracts: Puget Sound Power and Light Company, 1968-1980 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Contracts: Puget Sound Power and Light Company, 1980-1997 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Contracts: City of Richland Electric Department, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Contracts: Seattle Department of Lighting, 1950-1960 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Contracts: Seattle Department of Lighting, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Contracts: Seattle Department of Lighting, 1970-1994 (Box-folder 10/24)